uglyemail.com 2019-07-16

# Ugly Email - Privacy Policy.

### Privacy Policy

OneClick Lab built the Ugly Email app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by OneClick Lab at no cost and is intended for use as is. 

This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service. 

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Ugly Email unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy. 

**Information Collection and Use**

For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that we request is will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy. 

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

**Log Data**

We want to inform you that Ugly Email does not store, log, transfer, transmit or save any of your data.

**Service Providers**

We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

  * To facilitate our Service;
  * To provide the Service on our behalf;
  * To perform Service-related services; or
  * To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose. 

**Links to Other Sites**

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
